Guide to the Duke Forest Records, 1931-ongoing UA.10.09.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2018.0073, 2
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): FACTS I Project Description, 1995 October (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): FACTS 1 Annual Report (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): Blackwood Tower: EPA Blackwood, 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): NASA/Radar: Radar Imagery Eric Kasischke (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): Christensen JPL Proposal to NASA (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): Kasischke, Eric Student Ground Truth Program (Box 55)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): FACTS I Publicity and Research Information (Box 56)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): Kno, Ken Blackwood Division Research Files Invoices 1978 Timber Sale (Box 56)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): Blackwood Field Steve Piccot Southern Research Institute (Box 56)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): Katul Gabriel and Geron, Chris Blackwood Division Opend Field, Micromet, FACE Prototype Literature (Box 56)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): Oren, Ram Blackwood Divison Research File (Box 56)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): FACTS I GIS Map File (Box 56)
  - Research Projects (Blackwood): FACTS I GPS Data (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Xline (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Unique Species and Habitats (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Management Plan Background Info Meetings (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Goal Programming (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Timber Management (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Integrated Pest Management (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Ohmann (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Recreation/SocIIology (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Water Quality (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Information Management (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Bollinger (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Kanasakie (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Consuletti (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Foreman (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Tsou (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Wildlife Managemnet (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: MacKiernan, 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Draft Management Plan, 1980 December (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Species List Janet Ohmann (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Management Plan (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Management Plan Final, 1981 December (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Proposed Bike Path/Route (has large folded drawings) (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Path Golf Course (has large folded drawings) (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: 76-77 Annual Report Growth Data, 1976-1977 (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: 76-77 Data Eno, 1976-1977 (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Inventory Field Data (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Duke Forest Summary Area Vegetation Types (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: 76-77 Rough Draft, 1976-1977 (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Committee on Duke Forest, 1971 (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Budget 73-74/Forest 74-75, 1973-1975 (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Regeneration Areas 1967 Dur-Kor-Hills (Box 56)
  - Management Plan Case Studies: Forest Use All Departments Ed and Res (Box 56)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Completed Forms 01-02, 2001-2002 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Mailing Lists 01-02, 2001-2002 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Correspondence 01-02, 2001-2002 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Correspondence 2000-2001, 2001-2002 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Additional Project Information 2000-2001 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Mailing Lists 2000-2001 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Correspondence 99-2000, 1999-2000 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Report Summaries 99-2000, 1999-2000 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Mailing Lists 99-2000, 1999-2000 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Blank Report Forms 99-2000, 1999-2000 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Project Counts, 1999-2000 (Box 57)
    February meeting with Trustee Ed Sidman
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Additional Project Information 1999-2000 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1998-1999 Correspondence (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1998-1999 Mailing Lists (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1998-1999 Blank Forms (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1997-1998 Questionnaires Summaries (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1997-1998 Completed Questionnaires (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Additional Project information 1997-1998 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Correspondence 1997-1998 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Mailing Lists 1997-1998 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Blank Questionnaires and Guidelines 1997-1998 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1996-1997 Questionnaires Summaries (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1996-1997 Completed Questionnaires (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Correpsondence 1996-1997 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Mailing Lists 1996-1997 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Deer Survey Responses 1996-1997 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1995-1996 Blanks (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1995-1996 Questionnaires (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1994-1995 Questionnaires (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: General, 1994-1995 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1994-1995 Final Reports (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1993-1994 Questionnaires, 2 folders (Box 57)
    (including Vol. 2)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Blanks, 1993-1994 (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1992-1993 Questionnaires (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1991-1992 Questionnaires (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1990-1991 Questionnaires (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 1989-1990 Questionnaires (Box 57)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Questionnaires, 1988-1989 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Questionnaires, 1987-1988 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 86-87 Questionnaires from Lynn McGuries ?Non-Market Value Class, 1986-1987 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 86-87 Questionnaires, 1986-1987 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Spring 87 Research Survey, 1987 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 85-86 Questionnaires, 1985-1986 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 84-85 Questionnaires, 1984-1985 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 83-84 Questionnaires, 1983-1984 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: 82-83 Questionnaires, 1982-1983 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Research Questionnaires 82, 1982 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Research Questionnaires 81, 1981 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Research Questionnaires 80, 1980 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Research Questionnaires 79, 1979 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Blanks 78, 1978 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Questionnaires: Duke Forest General Forest Locations 78, 1978 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Questionaires: Durham Division 78, 1978 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: questionaires: Korstian Division 78, 1978 (Box 58)
  - Teaching and Research Questionnaires: Research Survey 77, 1978 (Box 58)
  - Aerial Photos: Korstian Division, 1951-1985; undated (Box 58)
  - Stand Records, 1931; 7 folders (Box 58)
  - Aerial Photos: Korstian Division/Durham Division, 1951 (Box 58)
  - Aerial Photos: Korstian Division, 1951; 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Aerial Photos: Korstian Extras, 1974; 7 folders (Box 58)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerial Indicies, 1997- (Box 58)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials: Hillsbourugh Division, 1951 February 26; 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials: Eno Division, 1951 February 26; 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials: Blackwood Division, 1951 February 26; 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials: Oosting Natural Area, 1951 February 26 (Box 58)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials: Durham Division, 1951 February 26; 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials: Durham Division/West Campus, 1951 February 26 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials: West/East Campus, 1951 February 23 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials: Paul River Division, 1951 February 05 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Unlabeled, 1951 February (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials 1959 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials: Durham Division, 1959 March 23 (Box 59)
    includes index
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials: Line 1 1959 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials: Line 2 1959 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 3 1959 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 4A 1959 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 4B 1959 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 5 1959 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 6 1959 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 5 Durham, 1961 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 6 Durham, 1961 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 5 Korstian, 1961 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 7 Korstian/Widener, 1961 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 8 Oosting, 1961 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 9 Blackwood, 1961 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 10 Blackwood, 1961 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 11 Blackwood, 1961 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 12 Hillsborough, 1961 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 13 Hillsborough, 1961 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 1-4 Durham, 1961; 4 folders (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Haw River, 1965; 3 folders (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 1 Hillsborough, 1966; 2 folders (Box 59)
    (includes index and unknown)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 2 Durham, 1966; 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 3 East Campus, 1966; 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Haw River, 1966 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Durham Division, 1977 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Durham Division/Eno River, 1969 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: 1969, 4 (Box 59)
    (labelling on images)
  - Aerial Photos: Extra Aerials: Hillsborough, 1974; 3 (Box 59)
    (index and notes)
  - Aerial Photos: Blackwood, 1974; 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Durham, 1974; 9 folders (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Eno and Natural Area, 1974 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: All Dark Photos (line 4-6), 1974; 4 folders (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: line 7-10, 1974; 4 folders (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials 75, 1975; 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 14-16 April Refly, 1985; 3 folders (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Line 1 and 2, 1993 (Box 59)
  - Aerial Photos: Aerials: Hurricane Damage, 1997 (Box 59)
  - Reading Files: Reading Files, 1978-1983; 8 folders (Box 59)
  - Reading Files: Reading Files, 1982-1994; 23 folders (Box 60)
  - Reading Files: Reading Files, 1994-2008 (Box 61)
    no 2001
  - Photographs: Permanent Sample Plot 1-Permanent Sample Plot 40 (Box 62)
  - Photographs: Permanent Sample Plot 41-Permanent Sample Plot 88, also Forest Service plot 14 (Box 63)
  - Photographs: Arboretum (Box 64)
  - Photographs: Loblolly Pine (Box 64)
  - Photographs: Loblolly Pine: Oak (Box 64)
  - Photographs: Loblolly Pine: Redgum (Box 64)
  - Photographs: Loblolly Pine: Shortleaf Pine (Box 64)
  - Photographs: Post Oak-Blackjack Oak (Box 64)
  - Photographs: Redgum-Yellow Poplar (Box 64)
  - Photographs: Riverbirch-Sycamore (Box 64)
  - Photographs: Shortleaf Pine (Box 64)
  - Photographs: Shortleaf Pine-Oak (Box 64)
  - Photographs: White Oak Black Oak Red Oak (Box 64)
  - Photographs: White Oak-Post Oak (Box 64)
  - Photographs: Unlabeled Trees (Box 64)
  - Photographs: Erosion Control (Box 64)
  - Photographs: Unlabled Trees (Box 65)
  - Photographs: Tree Poisoning (Box 65)
  - Photographs: Stand Conversion (Box 65)
  - Photographs: Release Cuttings (Box 65)
  - Photographs: Planting, Locus Borer (Box 65)
  - Photographs: Finning (Box 65)
  - Photographs: Pruning (Box 65)
  - Photographs: Other Injuries (Box 65)
  - Photographs: Fire Protection (Box 65)
  - Photographs: Lumbering and Utilization (Box 65)
  - Photographs: Smith Island and Sea (Box 65)
  - Photographs: Sand Dune Fixation (Box 65)
  - Photographs: Sand Dune Fixation (Box 66)
  - Photographs: Systems of Natural Generation- G.E.B. (Box 66)
  - Photographs: Systems of Natural Regeneration (Box 66)
  - Photographs: Systems of Natural Regeneration (Box 67)
  - Photographs: Systems of Natural Regeneration (Box 68)
  - Photographs: Systems of Natural Regeneration (Box 69)
  - Photographs: Research Projects: Trenching Study 1-3 (Box 69)
  - Photographs: Research Porojects: Trenching Study 4-7 (Box 70)
  - Research Projects: Shortleaf Pine Site Study (Box 70)
  - Honeysuckle Eradication (Box 70)
  - Firewound Studies (Box 70)
  - Photographs: Silviculture Research (Box 70)
  - Root Studies (Box 70)
  - Geology and Soils (Box 71)
  - Wood Anatomy and Properties (Box 71)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 71)
  - Improvements (Box 71)
  - Springs (Box 71)
  - Roads (Box 71)
  - Bridges (Box 71)
  - Houses (Box 71)
  - Shade and Street Tree Planting (Box 72)
  - School Facilities and Activities (Box 72)
  - Miscellaneous School of Forestry (Box 72)
  - Tree Sample Slides, 3 boxes (Box 72)
  - Miscellaneous Prints and Negatives (Box 73)
  - Slides (Box 74)
  - Notebooks, 4 items (Box 74)
  - Bloden Lake, 2002 June 10; VHS (Box 74)
  - Duke Forest Helicopter Logging Tape, VHS (Box 74)
  - Duke Forest Helicopter Logging (Original) Wendy and Olympics, VHS (Box 74)
  - Bill Rockwell D8 0:48, VHS (Box 74)
  - Sawmill, Nels Anderson, Hillsborough, DVD (Box 74)
  - Hill Forest, 2002 June 11; VHS (Box 74)
  - Duke Forest Helicopter Logging, VHS (Box 74)
  - LSC Public Info Meeting, VHS (Box 74)
  - LSC Public Info Meeting, 1995 April 05; VHS (Box 74)
  - Helicopter Logging Duke, 1997 May; VHS (Box 74)
  - Duke Forest, VHS (Box 74)
  - Forestry: Keeping North Carolina Green and Growing, VHS (Box 74)
  - BMPs for Logging Skid Trails, VHS (Box 74)
  - Duke Forest, 2002 May 30; VHS (Box 74)
  - Edeburn Duke Forest History, Optical disc (Box 74)
  - Duke Forest Research History Norm Christensen, 2003 March 21; Optical disc (Box 74)
  - Duke Forest Oral Histories, 1987 August 25-2003 February 12; Optical disc (Box 74)
  - Froest Interviews, 2002 July 30; Optical disc (Box 74)
  - Duke Forest Audio 2, 2002 July 10; Optical disc (Box 74)
  - BMPs for Logging Skid Trails, DVD (Box 74)
  - Family history from M. J. Hall, Optical disc (Box 74)
  - Judd Edeburn, Optical disc (Box 74)
  - Judd Edeburn, Duke Forest, Optical disc (Box 74)
  - Western Field Trip photos, 2004-2005; Optical disc (Box 74)
  - Western Field Trip photos, 2003; Optical disc (Box 74)
  - Aerial photographs roll (Box 74)
  - Carousel slide trays with slides, 3 items (Box 75)
  - Miscellaneous negatives in sleeves, labeled (35mm) (Box 75)
  - Loblolly pine logging photographs, 1927; 3 folders (Box 76)
  - Presentation photos, circa 1980s (Box 76)
  - Aerial photography notes, 1970s-1980s; 7 folders (Box 76)
  - Carousel slide trays with slides, 2 items (Box 76)
  - Aerial photographic negatives (Box 76)
    9x9 negatives in box
  - Air Photo Supply glasses (Box 76)
  - Planting/Forest notes (Box 77)
  - Photographic prints, 1980-1998 (Box 77)
  - Photographic prints, 1980-1998 (Box 78)
  - Photographic prints, 1998 Summer-undated (Box 78)
  - B&W Aerials 1:800 (glossy and matte), 1997 February (Box 79)
  - B&W Aerials 1:400 matte Hurricane fran damage, 1996 October (Box 79)
  - B&W 1:1000 Weyerhauser, 1994 March (Box 79)
  - B&W 1:800 hillsbourough division tornado damage, 1993 (Box 79)
  - Slides for Slideshow (Box 79)
  - Color Infrared 1:800, 1996 October (Box 80)
  - B&W Aerials 1:400 glossy hurricane fran damage, 1996 October (Box 80)
  - CF Korstian 35 mm Duke Forest slide collection, 1973 June 29 (Box 80)
  - Originals B&W Glossy and Original Aerials 1:800, 1985 January (Box 81)
  - Duke Forest, 1974 (Box 81)
  - Originals B&W Glossy and Original Aerials 1:800, 1974 (Box 81)
  - Duke Forest PSP and Lantern Slides (Box 81)
  - Duke Forest Miscelleanous Negatives and Prints (Box 82)
  - FACE/FACTS EXPT, circa 1996 (Box 82)
  - Assorted Notebooks (Sale and Survey), 10 Volumes (Box 82)
  - Possible Humidity Equipment (Box 82)
  - 10 Negatives rolled in aluminum cases, 10 items (Box 82)
  - FSCL VHS, circa 1994; 9 items; VHS (Box 83)
  - Ecosystem Management (Box 83)
  - Oscada Burns Wade, 1984 February (Box 83)
  - Jekyll Island, 1991 July (Box 83)
  - Aerial Proscribed Burning Project (Box 83)
  - Block B ENP Films, 7 items (Box 83)
  - Assorted Financial Ledgers, 2 items (Box 84)
  - Assorted Ledgers (Box 85)
  - Assorted Photos, Cassettes, Slides (Box 86)
  - Ledgers, 2 Volumes (Box 87)
  - Ledgers (Box 88)
  - Ledgers (Box 89)
  - Ledgers (Box 90)
  - Mounted photographs one still in frame (Box 91)
  - Ledger/ Large photograph album (Box 92)
  - The Jolly Woodlander, 1969 (Box 93)
  - Glass slides of tree samples, etc. (Box 94)
    1 small boxes, 3 small loose packages
  - Forest for the Future, 16mm (Box 95)
  - Clearing for Production Sales Training, 16mm (Box 95)
  - The Price, International Paper Company, 16mm (Box 95)
  - Fate of the Forest, Shell Oil, 16mm (Box 95)
  - Forests Are For People, American Forest Institute/Southern Forest Institute, 16mm (Box 95)
  - To Touch the Sky, Weyehaeuser, 2 items; 16mm (Box 95)
  - Glass slides of tree samples, etc. (Box 96)
    2 small boxes
- Accession UA2018.0094, 3
  - Blackwood, Eno, Hillsboro Special Projects (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Blackwood, Eno, Hillsboro Special Projects (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Blackwood, Eno, Hillsboro Special Projects (Oversize-folder 3)
  - Durham base maps and locations, 1975 (Oversize-folder 4)
  - Durham base maps and locations, 1952; 1963 (Oversize-folder 5)
  - Durham base maps and locations, 1931; 1944 (Oversize-folder 6)
  - Korstian base maps and operations, 1975; 1986 (Oversize-folder 7)
  - Korstian base maps and operations, 1931; 1944; 1952; 1963 (Oversize-folder 8)
  - Aerial photographs (Oversize-folder 9)
  - Haw River, Dodson's Crossroads, Dailey Tract, Special Projects (Oversize-folder 9)
  - poster board with photos (Oversize-folder 9)
  - Duke Forest Korstian Division (Oversize-folder 9)
  - Blackwood, Eno, Hillsborough special projects (Oversize-folder 10)
  - Korstian special projects (Oversize-folder 11)
  - Korstian special projects (Oversize-folder 12)
  - Blackwood, Eno, Hillsborough Base Maps and Operations, 1975; 1986 (Oversize-folder 13)
  - Blackwood, Eno, Hillsborough Base Maps and Operations, 1931; 1944; 1952; 1963 (Oversize-folder 14)
  - USGS Topo Quads for Duke Forest (Oversize-folder 15)
  - Duke Forest Location maps (Oversize-folder 16)
  - Mylars and Originals (Oversize-folder 17)
    includes giant negatives
  - Durham base maps and operations, 1986 (Oversize-folder 18)
  - Korstian soil/compartments (Oversize-folder 18)
  - Durham: Special Projects (Oversize-folder 19)
  - Korstian--Property (Oversize-folder 20)
  - Campus Projects (Oversize-folder 21)
  - Dodson's Crossroads, Dailey Tract: Base Maps and Operations (Oversize-folder 21)
  - Reference maps (Oversize-folder 22)
  - Durham Property (1 of 2) (Oversize-folder 23)
  - Durham Property (2 of 2) (Oversize-folder 24)
  - Blackwood, Eno, Hillsborough property (Oversize-folder 25)
  - Haw River Property, Compartments (Oversize-folder 26)
  - Dawson's Crossroads, Dailey Tract Property (Oversize-folder 26)
  - Aerial photographs: New Hope Creek Division, Hillsboro division (Volume 1)
  - Aerial photographs: Durham County (Volume 2)
  - Soil Maps: Duke Forest, undated (Box 96)
  - Soil Maps: Durham Division (tracings), undated (Box 96)
  - Soil Maps: Durham Division (copies), undated (Box 96)
  - Soil Maps: Durham Division (copies), undated (Box 96)
  - Forest Maps: New Hope Creek Division, undated (Box 96)
  - Negatives and PMTs of Selected Soil Maps of Durham Division, circa 1978 (Box 97)
  - Durham and Duke Forest Soils and Compartments, 1954; undated (Box 97)
  - Compartment Maps: Durham Division, undated (Box 97)
  - Hogan Plantation, undated (Box 97)
  - Blackwood, Eno, Hillsborough division maps, undated (Box 97)
  - Forest Maps: Hillsboro Division, undated (Box 97)
  - Soils Maps; Durham Division (prints), 1959; undated (Box 98)
  - Soils Maps; Durham Division (prints), undated (Box 98)
  - Soils Maps; Durham Division (prints), undated (Box 98)
  - Soils Maps; Durham Division (prints), undated (Box 98)
  - Korstian Soil Maps, undated (Box 99)
  - Korstian Soil Maps, undated (Box 99)
  - Hillsboro Division tornado damage, 1992-1993 (Box 100)
  - Landwood Blackwood Special Project, undated (Box 100)
  - Trenching Studies, 1932-1936; 1938; 2 folders (Box 100)
    Includes topographical map of portion of Durham Division.
  - Aerial photographic negatives of Duke Forest, 1974 (Box 100)
- Accession UA2019.0079, circa 1930s-1950s
  - 1934 Rainfall Data (Box 101)
  - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 101)
  - 1930s Cover Mapping (Box 101)
  - Compartment Cover Summaries, 1930s (Box 101)
  - Taxonomy of Special Groups, Musei Durham Division- Areas- West of Browning's Branch- Forest Types by Age Class, 1930s (Box 101)
  - Piedmont Vegetation, 1930s (Box 101)
  - Prim - Bottomland, 1930s (Box 101)
  - Bottomland Hardwood, 1930s (Box 101)
  - Loblolly Pine Durham, 1942 (Box 101)
  - Lob - Sh - Pine Tallies, 1942 (Box 101)
  - Bottomland Pine, 1942 (Box 101)
  - Oak - Hickory - Oosting 1942 Data Collection 1935 (Box 101)
  - Old Field, 1942 (Box 101)
  - Oak - Hickory Density and Frequency, 1940s-1950s (Box 101)
  - Oak Hickory Original Field Data, 1940s-1950s (Box 101)
  - Shortleaf Pine, Durham DV, 1940s-1950s (Box 101)
  - Loblolly Pine, N.H.C., 1940s-1950s (Box 101)
  - Mixed Pine Hardwoods, 1940s-1950s (Box 101)
  - Catsbury Post Climax - 2 Series 816, 1940s-1950s (Box 101)
  - Upland hardwood- Durham Division, 1940s-1950s (Box 101)
  - 1930s Compartment Maps (Box 101)
  - Durham Compartment Maps, 1930s (Box 101)
  - Hillsboro Compartment Maps, 1930s (Box 101)
  - New Hope Creek Compartment Maps, 1930s (Box 101)
  - 1930s Inventory (Box 101)
  - Vol Summary - by Types and Age Classes, and by Types, 1930s (Box 101)
  - Volume Summary Durham E. Sand Cr. - by Types and Age Classes and by Types, 1930s (Box 101)
  - Height Curves, 1930s (Box 101)
  - Division Map 8, 1930s (Box 101)
  - Volume Tables, Originals, (Untyped), 1930s (Box 101)
  - Volume Tables, Original, (Typed), 1930s (Box 101)
  - Volume Tables, Carbons, 1930s (Box 101)
  - List of Volume Tables Used, 1930s (Box 101)
  - Compartment Summary, September 1, 1931 (Box 101)
  - 1942 Inventory - Instructions, Volume Tables, etc. (Box 101)
  - 1952 Inventory: Blackwood Division Cruise -1952 (Box 101)
  - Couch Tract Cruise - 1952 (Box 101)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 14, Comp 21, 34, 35 and Small Area of 33 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 15, Compartment 22-23 (Arboretum) (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 17, Compartment 26 (Arboretum) (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 18, Compartment 27 - 28 (Arboretum) (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 20, Comp 31, 32, 33 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 21, Comp 38, 39 (area between these comp) (Box 102)